<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Manage money. Together. on Econumo</title><link>https://econumo.com/</link><description>Recent content in Manage money. Together. on Econumo</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://econumo.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CSV Import &amp; Export</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/csv-import-export/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/csv-import-export/</guid><description>CSV Import &amp;amp; Export # This section provides an overview of &amp;lsquo;CSV Import &amp;amp; Export&amp;rsquo; in Econumo.
In this section # Exporting your transactions to CSV Importing transactions from CSV Exporting your transactions to CSV # You can export your transactions to a CSV file for use in other applications or for backup purposes.
To export your transactions:
Navigate to &amp;ldquo;Settings&amp;rdquo; Click on &amp;ldquo;Export CSV&amp;rdquo; Select the account(s) you want to export transactions from.</description></item><item><title>v0.7.0 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.7.0-release/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.7.0-release/</guid><description>The v0.7.0 release introduces PostgreSQL support in beta. Since it’s still in beta, it has performance issues, so it’s not recommended for use.
GitHub releases # Econumo CE: v0.7.0</description></item><item><title>v0.6.0 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.6.0-release/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.6.0-release/</guid><description>The v0.6.0 release features a complete rewrite of how Econumo handles numbers and currencies. This update allows the system to utilize the specified number of fraction digits for each currency (8 maximum), ensuring precise budget conversions, even for older periods.
After deploying this version, it is recommended to run the following command:
docker-compose exec -u www-data econumo bin/console app:restore-currency-fraction-digits Changelog # Enhanced the command docker-compose exec -u www-data econumo bin/console app:add-currency --help, enabling you to specify a custom name and the number of fraction digits for any currency, including Bitcoin.</description></item><item><title>v0.5.2 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.5.2-release/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.5.2-release/</guid><description>The v0.5.2 release primarily includes bug fixes and minor improvements based on feedback from the Reddit community following the announcement of Econumo CE.
Changelog # Fixed the bug related to multiple currencies without their exchange rates. GitHub releases # Econumo CE: v0.5.2</description></item><item><title>v0.5.1 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.5.1-release/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.5.1-release/</guid><description>The v0.5.1 release primarily includes bug fixes and minor improvements based on feedback from the Reddit community following the announcement of Econumo CE.
Changelog # Fixed the display of multiple expense transactions with the same category in the budget. Added a placeholder for the transaction entry form. Resolved issues with the date range functionality in the budget. Added a &amp;ldquo;Shared Access&amp;rdquo; page to Econumo CE. Fixed the /api/v1/system/import-currency-rates endpoint to update existing exchange rates without returning a 500 error.</description></item><item><title>Debug Econumo</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/self-hosting/debug/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/self-hosting/debug/</guid><description> Overview # Econumo uses the following HTTP response codes:
HTTP 2xx - Indicates that everything is fine. HTTP 4xx - Indicates errors related to the user&amp;rsquo;s input. HTTP 5xx - Indicates server errors. How to debug 5xx errors # If you encounter a 500 HTTP error code, use the following command to check the application&amp;rsquo;s logs:
docker-compose exec -u www-data econumo tail -f /var/www/var/log/prod.log</description></item><item><title>Tweaking the backend</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/self-hosting/tweaking-backend/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/self-hosting/tweaking-backend/</guid><description>Tweaking the backend # WARNING! In general, tweaking is not recommended; please do so at your own risk. If you are familiar with PHP and Symfony, you can add functionality to the backend, such as:
Custom CLI commands; New APIs; Additional handlers for domain events. However, keep in mind that your code may break at some point due to changes in the Econumo codebase.
How to do that # Econumo uses a modified Symfony Kernel to load all Bundles from src folder.</description></item><item><title>Tweaking the frontend</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/self-hosting/tweaking-frontend/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/self-hosting/tweaking-frontend/</guid><description>Tweaking the frontend # WARNING! In general, tweaking is not recommended; please do so at your own risk. Econumo uses the JavaScript tag manager LilTag, allowing you to inject any JavaScript code into your Econumo instance.
I use this mechanism to show a warning message on demo.econumo.com and to inject analytics scripts.
In this guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll inject the following script into your Econumo:
&amp;lt;script&amp;gt;console.log(&amp;#39;Injected!&amp;#39;);&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt; Configuration # Step 1 # Add the following environment variables to your .</description></item><item><title>Econumo API</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/api/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/api/</guid><description>Econumo API # Econumo includes a REST API and OpenAPI (Swagger) documentation.
The Swagger UI is accessible at the api/doc URL. For example, in the demo environment, it can be found here: https://demo.econumo.com/api/doc.
The documentation features only GET and POST HTTP methods. The GET method is used for reading data, while the POST method is used for modifying data (creating, changing, or deleting).
In this section # Econumo System API Econumo User API System endpoints Health check Econumo System API # All methods under /api/v1/system are part of the System API.</description></item><item><title>Econumo apps</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/apps/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/apps/</guid><description>Econumo APPs # Econumo is a web application, but you can also use it as a regular mobile application on your iPhone, Android device, Mac, or PC.
On iPhone: # Open the website https://app.econumo.com in Safari. Tap the Share button (square with an upward arrow). Select Add to Home Screen from the menu. Rename the shortcut if desired, then tap Add. The web app will appear on your home screen and open in its own instance.</description></item><item><title>v0.5.0 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.5.0-release/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.5.0-release/</guid><description>Changelog # Added user onboarding. Added more icons for categories. Added a calculator widget for the transaction dialog. Refactored logic related to budget loading. Refactored the BudgetAccessModal component. Refactored the BudgetChangeCurrency component. Improved handling of the long-press directive. Fixed issue where new envelopes were created in the second position instead of the first. Corrected currency conversion for the &amp;ldquo;Available&amp;rdquo; field in the budget module. Fixed bug that occurred when clearing cache after deleting a budget.</description></item><item><title>CLI (terminal) commands</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/self-hosting/cli-commands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/self-hosting/cli-commands/</guid><description> CLI (terminal) commands # Econumo provides several CLI commands that are useful for managing the application.
List of available commands # Application specific: # docker-compose exec -u www-data econumo bin/console | grep app: All available commands: # docker-compose exec -u www-data econumo bin/console CLI commands # Add a new currency # docker-compose exec -u www-data econumo bin/console app:add-currency --help Create a user # docker-compose exec -u www-data econumo bin/console app:create-user --help Change user e-mail # docker-compose exec -u www-data econumo bin/console app:change-user-email --help Change user password # docker-compose exec -u www-data econumo bin/console app:change-user-password --help</description></item><item><title>Accounts</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/accounts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/accounts/</guid><description>Accounts # This section covers basics of &amp;lsquo;Accounts&amp;rsquo; in Econumo.
Accounts represents your accounts in financial institutions. For example, &amp;ldquo;Savings account&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Cash&amp;rdquo;.
In this section # Account creation Managing your accounts Organize accounts in folders Ordering folders Hiding folders Shared access Account creation # To create a new account in Econumo, specify the account name, current balance, currency, and icon.
Once the account is created, it will appear in the left sidebar:</description></item><item><title>Budgets</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/budgets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/budgets/</guid><description>Budgets # This section introduces the basics of &amp;lsquo;Budgets&amp;rsquo; in Econumo.
Budgets enable you to implement a &amp;ldquo;Cash Stuffing&amp;rdquo; method, also known as the envelope budgeting approach, which uses envelopes to manage spending.
The concept is straightforward: Take a few envelopes, label each with an expense category—such as groceries, rent, or car loan—and place the amount of money you plan to spend in each envelope. This way, you set limits on your spending for each category.</description></item><item><title>Classifications</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/classifications/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/classifications/</guid><description>Classifications # This section introduces the basics of &amp;lsquo;Classifications&amp;rsquo; in Econumo, including Categories, Tags, and Payees. All three entities share similar functionalities:
Create a new item. Update or delete an existing item. Archive or unarchive any item. In this section # Create a category, tag, or payee Update or delete Archive or unarchive Create a category, tag, or payee # To create a new item, go to Settings -&amp;gt; Categories / Payees / Tags and click on the Create button.</description></item><item><title>Shared Access</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/shared-access/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/shared-access/</guid><description>Shared Access # Note
Please note that &amp;ldquo;Shared access&amp;rdquo; page is only available for Econumo (cloud) version. This section provides an overview of &amp;lsquo;Shared Access&amp;rsquo; in Econumo.
Econumo enables users to connect with each other to share access to various accounts and budgets.
In this section # Connect with another user Remove connection between users Check shared accounts and budgets Connect with another user # When you connect with another Econumo user, you aren&amp;rsquo;t sharing anything yet.</description></item><item><title>Transactions</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/transactions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/transactions/</guid><description>Transactions # This section provides an overview of &amp;lsquo;Transactions&amp;rsquo; in Econumo.
Transactions form the core of Econumo, as all budgeting is based on the transactions you enter.
In this section # Adding transactions Adding expenses Adding transfers Adding income Editing a transaction Deleting a transaction Adding transactions # Transaction date
In the top right corner, you can specify the transaction date (the date you spent or earned the money). Clicking on the date will open a calendar.</description></item><item><title>User Profile</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/user-profile/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/user-profile/</guid><description>User profile # This section provides an overview of &amp;lsquo;User Profiles&amp;rsquo; in Econumo.
In this section # Accessing your user profile Updating your user profile How to change your email How to change your username How to change your avatar Accessing your user profile # You can access your profile details by clicking on your avatar in the left sidebar. Alternatively, go to Settings and click on your avatar there.</description></item><item><title>Backups</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/self-hosting/backups/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/self-hosting/backups/</guid><description>Backups # Econumo CE does not come with a built-in backup mechanism; it is your responsibility to configure backups for your instance.
Econumo CE stores its data in SQLite, so it is easy to configure a regularly back up of your database. Consider the following well-known options in the SQLite community for effective backup management.
Regular Cron-based backups # For personal use, a regular cron-based backup may be sufficient. You can find a straightforward guide on setting this up here: https://litestream.</description></item><item><title>v0.4.3 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.4.3-release/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.4.3-release/</guid><description> Changelog # Added &amp;ldquo;Total&amp;rdquo; amount to the budgeting module. GitHub releases # Econumo CE: v0.4.3</description></item><item><title>v0.4.1 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.4.1-release/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.4.1-release/</guid><description> Changelog # Updated email content. Added the ECONUMO_BASE_URL environment variable. Fixed a bug related to the default locale. GitHub releases # Econumo CE: v0.4.1</description></item><item><title>v0.4.0 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.4.0-release/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.4.0-release/</guid><description>Changelog # Added a registration feature and updated the configuration and login layout. Corrected the translation for &amp;ldquo;All accounts.&amp;rdquo; Fixed budget calculations for individual users. Resolved issues with the modal window displaying the transaction list for budgets. Introduced user avatars in the transaction list modal for budgets. Fixed a bug that displayed ghost transactions when a user changed a transaction type. Improved the currency selection box in the Budget module.</description></item><item><title>v0.3.0 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.3.0-release/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.3.0-release/</guid><description> Changelog # Econumo Family and Econumo One merged into Econumo CE and were fully open-sourced. Econumo Cloud became Econumo. Fixed a problem with currency rates for the Budget module. GitHub releases # Econumo CE: v0.3.0</description></item><item><title>v0.2.3 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.2.3-release/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.2.3-release/</guid><description> Changelog # Disabled a portion of the login form for the custom backend API URL Updated links to the Privacy Policy and Terms of Service pages Added edition to the logo GitHub releases # Econumo CE: v0.2.3</description></item><item><title>v0.2.2 Econumo hotfix</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.2.2-release/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.2.2-release/</guid><description> Changelog # Rollback of the dependency update in composer.lock that broke authentication GitHub releases # Econumo CE: v0.2.2</description></item><item><title>v0.2.1 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.2.1-release/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.2.1-release/</guid><description> Changelog # Added functionality to connect registered users with one another automatically. GitHub releases # Econumo CE: v0.2.1</description></item><item><title>v0.2.0 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.2.0-release/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.2.0-release/</guid><description> Changelog # Removed the legacy PostgreSQL dependency. Added an X-Timezone header to each API request to maintain consistent time zones between the frontend and backend. Addressed all of Rector&amp;rsquo;s warnings. Removed the old analytics API. Update API documentation. GitHub releases # Econumo CE: v0.2.0</description></item><item><title>v0.1.0 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.1.0-release/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.1.0-release/</guid><description>The first public release of Econumo.
GitHub releases # Econumo CE: v0.1.0</description></item><item><title>Econumo Editions</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/edition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/edition/</guid><description>Econumo Editions # Econumo provides versatile editions to meet various needs:
Econumo # Suited for individuals and families seeking convenience and access, this cloud-hosted solution offers a comprehensive suite of financial management tools available anytime, anywhere.
Demo: https://demo.econumo.com Demo version is available for one week only. After this period, your demo account will be blocked.
Econumo CE (Community Edition) # Designed for households needing a self-hosted, collaborative approach. This free platform delivers powerful financial management features for those who prioritize privacy and control over their budgeting.</description></item><item><title>Multi-Currency support</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/self-hosting/multi-currency/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/self-hosting/multi-currency/</guid><description>Multi-Currency Support # Econumo offers multi-currency functionality. To get started, you need to:
Load currencies into your Econumo instance. Set up a daily update for exchange rates (if needed). How to add a new currency to Econumo # If you want to use a currency other than USD (the only preloaded currency in Econumo), simply run the following command (available since v0.5.1):
docker-compose exec -u www-data econumo bin/console app:add-currency --help If you want to add multiple currencies and require regular exchange rate updates, see the next step.</description></item><item><title>Contact us</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/contact-us/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/contact-us/</guid><description>Contact us # Please use GitHub discussions to talk about the roadmap, features, and bugs.
For billing-related inquiries or partnership opportunities, email econumo@gmail.com.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/faq/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/faq/</guid><description>Frequently Asked Questions # Do you have plans to add automated import of transactions from banks? # Automated import of transactions from banks and other sources is not a priority at this point. However, it might be added in the future as an optional feature.
If you have development skills and want to contribute, you are welcome to do so by using Econumo&amp;rsquo;s API.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://econumo.com/posts/346e5552-35d6-4741-87b6-824e9ebcb45a/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/346e5552-35d6-4741-87b6-824e9ebcb45a/</guid><description>Getting a handle on your household budget starts with a simple, honest chat. Before you get into the weeds of where your money should go, you and your partner need to sit down together, gather up all your income sources, and list out every single fixed expense. Think of it less as a math problem and more as the first step in teamwork. It’s all about creating a clear, shared picture of your financial starting point.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://econumo.com/posts/test-article-123/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/test-article-123/</guid><description>Sample Article # This is a test article content in Markdown format.
Introduction # This webhook test ensures your endpoint can receive and process article data correctly.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/legal/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/legal/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Privacy Policy # Introduction # Your privacy is important to us. It is Econumo&amp;rsquo;s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect from you across our website, econumo.com, its subdomains, and other sites we own and operate (collectively, the &amp;ldquo;Sites&amp;rdquo;). This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you visit any of our Sites. Please read this policy carefully to understand our practices regarding your information.</description></item><item><title>Terms of Service</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/legal/terms-of-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/legal/terms-of-service/</guid><description>Terms of Service # By using our websites, services, and products (collectively referred to as the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), you agree to these Terms of Service (&amp;ldquo;Terms&amp;rdquo;). Please read them carefully. If you do not agree, please discontinue using our Software.
1. Acceptance of Terms # By accessing or using Econumo, you confirm that you accept these Terms and agree to abide by them.
2. Effective Date # These Terms are effective from the date you first use the Econumo application.</description></item></channel></rss>