<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>How to Save Money on Econumo</title><link>https://econumo.com/tags/how-to-save-money/</link><description>Recent content in How to Save Money on Econumo</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:24:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://econumo.com/tags/how-to-save-money/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Modern Guide to the Cash Envelope Budgeting System</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/cash-envelope-budgeting-system/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:24:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/cash-envelope-budgeting-system/</guid><description>The cash envelope system is a simple, hands-on way to manage your money. You divide your cash for the month into different envelopes, each one labeled for a specific spending category like &amp;ldquo;Groceries&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Gas.&amp;rdquo; Once the cash in an envelope is gone, you&amp;rsquo;re done spending in that category until next month.
It’s a beautifully simple system that creates a real, physical connection to your spending and makes it almost impossible to overspend.</description></item><item><title>Your Free 100 Envelope Challenge Printable to Save $5,050</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/100-envelope-challenge-printable/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:22:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/100-envelope-challenge-printable/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever wanted a simple, hands-on way to save a serious chunk of cash, a 100 envelope challenge printable is your ticket to stashing away exactly $5,050. The whole idea is to turn saving money into a kind of game by using a tracker or labels numbered 1 to 100. You match the dollar amount to the number on the envelope and stuff it inside.
What Is the 100 Envelope Challenge # The 100 Envelope Challenge is a savings method that went viral for good reason—it transforms the vague idea of &amp;ldquo;saving more&amp;rdquo; into a physical, hands-on activity.</description></item><item><title>How Much to Save Per Paycheck (how much to save per paycheck): A Practical Guide</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/how-much-to-save-per-paycheck/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 06:47:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/how-much-to-save-per-paycheck/</guid><description>If you’ve ever wondered how much to save from each paycheck, you’re not alone. The classic rule of thumb is to aim for 20% of your take-home pay. This isn&amp;rsquo;t just a random number; it&amp;rsquo;s the savings portion of the popular 50/30/20 budget, a simple framework that can really build a strong financial foundation.
Think of it as the starting line. Hitting that 20% mark helps you get into the rhythm of paying yourself first, which is crucial for tackling debt, building an emergency fund, and investing for the long haul.</description></item></channel></rss>