<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Financial Planning on Econumo</title><link>https://econumo.com/tags/financial-planning/</link><description>Recent content in Financial Planning on Econumo</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 07:09:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://econumo.com/tags/financial-planning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Can You Have an IRA and a 401k? Supercharge Your Savings</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/can-you-have-an-ira-and-a-401-k/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 07:09:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/can-you-have-an-ira-and-a-401-k/</guid><description>Yes, you absolutely can have both an IRA and a 401(k) at the same time. This is one of the most common questions people ask when they start getting serious about retirement. The good news is, not only is it allowed, but for many people, it&amp;rsquo;s a fantastic strategy to really accelerate their savings.
Think of it as having two different but powerful tools in your financial workshop. Each one has its own job to do, and using them together can help you build a much stronger financial future.</description></item><item><title>7 Life-Changing Benefits of Paying Off Mortgage Early in 2026</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/benefits-of-paying-off-mortgage-early/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 07:40:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/benefits-of-paying-off-mortgage-early/</guid><description>For most households, a mortgage represents the largest and longest-lasting debt they will ever carry. The idea of owning your home free and clear might seem like a far-off milestone, but accelerating that timeline is a powerful financial move with far-reaching effects. The journey to paying off a mortgage early is a strategic decision that fundamentally reshapes your financial landscape, reduces long-term stress, and unlocks a new level of personal freedom.</description></item><item><title>A Practical Guide to Budgeting for Irregular Income</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/budgeting-for-irregular-income/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:53:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/budgeting-for-irregular-income/</guid><description>When your income swings up and down each month, standard budgeting advice can feel like it was written for a different planet. The key to getting a handle on things isn&amp;rsquo;t about guessing what you&amp;rsquo;ll earn next month. Instead, it&amp;rsquo;s about creating a rock-solid plan based on your absolute essentials.
This means building what I call a &amp;lsquo;bare-bones&amp;rsquo; budget. You figure out the bare minimum you need to get by and base your entire financial plan on that number.</description></item></channel></rss>