<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Budgeting Tools on Econumo</title><link>https://econumo.com/tags/budgeting-tools/</link><description>Recent content in Budgeting Tools on Econumo</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:14:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://econumo.com/tags/budgeting-tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Finding the Best Alternatives to Mint Finance</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/alternatives-to-mint-finance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 10:14:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/alternatives-to-mint-finance/</guid><description>With Mint&amp;rsquo;s shutdown official, many of us are looking for a new place to manage our money. The top alternatives to Mint finance are apps like Monarch Money, YNAB, and Tiller. These aren&amp;rsquo;t just simple replacements; they offer features that modern users actually need, like collaborative household budgeting, better privacy controls, and multi-currency support.
Navigating Your Finances After Mint # The end of Mint has left millions searching for a new financial home.</description></item><item><title>Your Guide to Self Hosted Budget Software</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/self-hosted-budget-software/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:48:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/self-hosted-budget-software/</guid><description>When you hear &amp;ldquo;self-hosted budget software,&amp;rdquo; you might think it&amp;rsquo;s something reserved for tech wizards. But the idea is actually pretty simple: it&amp;rsquo;s about taking back control of your financial data. Instead of handing your sensitive info over to a third-party cloud service, you run the budgeting app on your own private server.
It&amp;rsquo;s the difference between keeping your financial journal in a locked safe at home versus leaving it on a table in a public library.</description></item><item><title>A Complete Guide to Self Hosted Finance Manager Software</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/self-hosted-finance-manager/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:59:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/self-hosted-finance-manager/</guid><description>When you hear the term &amp;ldquo;self hosted finance manager,&amp;rdquo; what comes to mind? It’s simply finance software that you install and run on your own server. This gives you absolute control over your financial data.
Instead of handing over sensitive information like your income, expenses, and net worth to a third-party company, you become the sole gatekeeper. This approach ensures your data stays completely private, shielded from prying eyes, and free from recurring subscription fees.</description></item><item><title>The 12 Best Debt Payoff Apps of 2026 to Get Debt-Free Faster</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/best-debt-payoff-apps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 08:04:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/best-debt-payoff-apps/</guid><description>Tackling debt can feel overwhelming, but the right tool can turn a complex challenge into a clear, manageable plan. A dedicated debt payoff app helps you organize your loans, strategize your payments, and visualize your progress, providing the motivation needed to stay on track. These apps move you beyond simple spreadsheets by automating calculations for popular methods like the debt snowball or avalanche, showing you exactly how much time and money you can save.</description></item></channel></rss>