<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>User Guide on Econumo</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/</link><description>Recent content in User Guide on Econumo</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Accounts</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/accounts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/accounts/</guid><description>Accounts # This section covers basics of &amp;lsquo;Accounts&amp;rsquo; in Econumo.
Accounts represents your accounts in financial institutions. For example, &amp;ldquo;Savings account&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Cash&amp;rdquo;.
In this section # Account creation Managing your accounts Organize accounts in folders Ordering folders Hiding folders Shared access Account creation # To create a new account in Econumo, specify the account name, current balance, currency, and icon.
Once the account is created, it will appear in the left sidebar:</description></item><item><title>Budgets</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/budgets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/budgets/</guid><description>Budgets # This section introduces the basics of &amp;lsquo;Budgets&amp;rsquo; in Econumo.
Budgets enable you to implement a &amp;ldquo;Cash Stuffing&amp;rdquo; method, also known as the envelope budgeting approach, which uses envelopes to manage spending.
The concept is straightforward: Take a few envelopes, label each with an expense category—such as groceries, rent, or car loan—and place the amount of money you plan to spend in each envelope. This way, you set limits on your spending for each category.</description></item><item><title>Classifications</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/classifications/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/classifications/</guid><description> Classifications # Note
This documentation is currently in progress. Updates and additional sections will be added soon. Thank you for your patience!</description></item><item><title>Shared Access</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/shared-access/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/shared-access/</guid><description>Shared Access # Note
Please note that &amp;ldquo;Shared access&amp;rdquo; page is only available for Econumo (cloud) version. This section provides an overview of &amp;lsquo;Shared Access&amp;rsquo; in Econumo.
Econumo enables users to connect with each other to share access to various accounts and budgets.
In this section # Connect with another user Remove connection between users Check shared accounts and budgets Connect with another user # When you connect with another Econumo user, you aren&amp;rsquo;t sharing anything yet.</description></item><item><title>Transactions</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/transactions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/transactions/</guid><description>Transactions # This section provides an overview of &amp;lsquo;Transactions&amp;rsquo; in Econumo.
Transactions form the core of Econumo, as all budgeting is based on the transactions you enter.
In this section # Adding transactions Adding expenses Adding transfers Adding income Editing a transaction Deleting a transaction Adding transactions # Transaction date
In the top right corner, you can specify the transaction date (the date you spent or earned the money). Clicking on the date will open a calendar.</description></item><item><title>User Profile</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/user-profile/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/user-guide/user-profile/</guid><description>User profile # This section provides an overview of &amp;lsquo;User Profiles&amp;rsquo; in Econumo.
In this section # Accessing your user profile Updating your user profile How to change your email How to change your username How to change your avatar Accessing your user profile # You can access your profile details by clicking on your avatar in the left sidebar. Alternatively, go to Settings and click on your avatar there.</description></item></channel></rss>