<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Econumo</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Econumo</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 07:40:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://econumo.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Avoid Currency Conversion Fees When Traveling</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/how-to-avoid-currency-conversion-fees/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 07:40:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/how-to-avoid-currency-conversion-fees/</guid><description>Ever come home from a trip, looked at your credit card statement, and had that sinking feeling? The numbers just don&amp;rsquo;t add up. That beautiful €50 dinner in Rome somehow cost you $57, not the $54 you expected. You&amp;rsquo;ve just met the quiet thief of travel budgets: hidden currency conversion fees.
These little charges aren&amp;rsquo;t just a minor annoyance. They&amp;rsquo;re a real drain on your funds, especially on longer trips. Banks and payment processors often bake a markup of 3-5% into the exchange rates they give you.</description></item><item><title>International Money Transfer Comparison Finding the Best Rates</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/international-money-transfer-comparison/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 07:29:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/international-money-transfer-comparison/</guid><description>Sending money across borders can feel like a maze, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be. This guide offers a straightforward international money transfer comparison, breaking down the smoke and mirrors of exchange rates, hidden fees, and transfer speeds. I&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the process so you can confidently choose the right service, whether you&amp;rsquo;re supporting family back home, managing business abroad, or just paying for a vacation rental.
Finding the Best Way to Send Money Abroad # Choosing the right way to send money internationally is all about balancing cost, speed, and simple convenience.</description></item><item><title>A Guide to Open Source Personal Finance Software</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/open-source-personal-finance-software/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 07:22:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/open-source-personal-finance-software/</guid><description>So, what exactly is open source personal finance software? Put simply, it’s a type of financial tool where the source code—the very blueprint of the software—is open for anyone to see, use, and even improve upon.
Think of it like a community cookbook for managing your money. It&amp;rsquo;s completely transparent, you can tailor the recipes to your taste, and it isn&amp;rsquo;t controlled by a single corporate entity. This approach puts you in the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat, giving you total ownership of your financial data.</description></item><item><title>Your Free 100 Envelope Challenge Printable to Save $5,050</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/100-envelope-challenge-printable/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 07:22:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/100-envelope-challenge-printable/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever wanted a simple, hands-on way to save a serious chunk of cash, a 100 envelope challenge printable is your ticket to stashing away exactly $5,050. The whole idea is to turn saving money into a kind of game by using a tracker or labels numbered 1 to 100. You match the dollar amount to the number on the envelope and stuff it inside.
What Is the 100 Envelope Challenge # The 100 Envelope Challenge is a savings method that went viral for good reason—it transforms the vague idea of &amp;ldquo;saving more&amp;rdquo; into a physical, hands-on activity.</description></item><item><title>Principles of Finance: A Practical Guide for Family Budgeting</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/principles-of-finance/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 07:19:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/principles-of-finance/</guid><description>Think of financial principles not as rigid rules from a textbook, but as a reliable compass for navigating your family&amp;rsquo;s money journey. These are the core ideas that help you make smart, confident decisions about everything from daily spending to long-term goals. They cover concepts like the time value of money, risk and return, diversification, and much more.
Exploring the Core Principles of Finance for Families # In this guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll break down ten fundamental finance principles and translate them into practical, everyday steps you can take right now.</description></item><item><title>What Does Secured Bond Mean An Investor's Simple Guide</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/what-does-secured-bond-mean/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 07:04:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/what-does-secured-bond-mean/</guid><description>Ever wondered what a secured bond means? The easiest way to think about it is to compare it to a home mortgage. When you get a mortgage, the house itself acts as collateral. If you can&amp;rsquo;t make the payments, the bank has a claim on your house. A secured bond works on the same principle for investors.
A company or government entity that issues a secured bond pledges a specific, valuable asset—think a factory, a fleet of aircraft, or a portfolio of real estate—as a safety net for the investor.</description></item><item><title>v0.9.0 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.9.0-release/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.9.0-release/</guid><description>The v0.9.0 release introduces a fully open-source version of Econumo under a single repository, licensed under the MIT license.
Additionally, the release improves consistency in dialog window behaviour and provides an enhanced screen for shared access.
Changelog # Merged Econumo’s source code into a single repository. Changed the license from AGPLv3 to MIT. Improved dialog window consistency. Enhanced the shared access screen. Upgraded PHP to version 8.5. GitHub releases # Econumo: v0.</description></item><item><title>Can You Have an IRA and a 401k? Supercharge Your Savings</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/can-you-have-an-ira-and-a-401-k/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 07:09:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/can-you-have-an-ira-and-a-401-k/</guid><description>Yes, you absolutely can have both an IRA and a 401(k) at the same time. This is one of the most common questions people ask when they start getting serious about retirement. The good news is, not only is it allowed, but for many people, it&amp;rsquo;s a fantastic strategy to really accelerate their savings.
Think of it as having two different but powerful tools in your financial workshop. Each one has its own job to do, and using them together can help you build a much stronger financial future.</description></item><item><title>7 Life-Changing Benefits of Paying Off Mortgage Early in 2026</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/benefits-of-paying-off-mortgage-early/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 07:40:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/benefits-of-paying-off-mortgage-early/</guid><description>For most households, a mortgage represents the largest and longest-lasting debt they will ever carry. The idea of owning your home free and clear might seem like a far-off milestone, but accelerating that timeline is a powerful financial move with far-reaching effects. The journey to paying off a mortgage early is a strategic decision that fundamentally reshapes your financial landscape, reduces long-term stress, and unlocks a new level of personal freedom.</description></item><item><title>Boost Your Score: remove collections from credit report</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/remove-collections-from-credit-report/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 07:40:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/remove-collections-from-credit-report/</guid><description>Yes, you can absolutely get a collection removed from your credit report. The most common ways are by disputing errors, forcing the collector to validate the debt, or negotiating a &amp;ldquo;pay-for-delete&amp;rdquo; deal. And thanks to some recent industry changes, it&amp;rsquo;s gotten easier to remove certain debts, especially medical collections.
But first, you have to understand what you&amp;rsquo;re up against.
How Collections Really Affect Your Credit Score # That sinking feeling when a &amp;ldquo;collection&amp;rdquo; account suddenly appears on your credit report is real.</description></item><item><title>How to Improve Your Credit Score: Quick, Actionable Tips</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/how-to-improve-your-credit-score/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:59:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/how-to-improve-your-credit-score/</guid><description>If you want to improve your credit score, it really comes down to a few core habits: always pay your bills on time, keep your credit card balances low, and only apply for new credit when you actually need it. Get those three things right, and you&amp;rsquo;re building the foundation of a strong financial life by proving you&amp;rsquo;re a reliable borrower.
Your Quick Guide to a Better Credit Score # Trying to figure out how to raise your credit score can feel like you&amp;rsquo;re trying to solve a puzzle with half the pieces missing.</description></item><item><title>How to Pay Off Debt Faster and Find Financial Freedom</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/how-to-pay-off-debt-faster/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:14:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/how-to-pay-off-debt-faster/</guid><description>Getting out of debt faster really boils down to two things: knowing exactly what you owe and picking a smart plan to attack it. Before you do anything else, you need a crystal-clear picture of every single balance, minimum payment, and—most importantly—interest rate. Once you have that, you can decide whether the quick wins of the Debt Snowball method or the money-saving power of the Debt Avalanche method is the right fit for you.</description></item><item><title>How to Save for a House Your Practical Home Buying Guide</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/save-for-a-house/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 07:05:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/save-for-a-house/</guid><description>Before you can start stashing cash away, the first step in your home-buying journey begins with a question: what does &amp;ldquo;home&amp;rdquo; actually look like for you? A vague idea of a &amp;ldquo;nice house in a good neighborhood&amp;rdquo; won&amp;rsquo;t cut it. To build a savings plan that actually works, you need a crystal-clear vision you can slap a price tag on.
What&amp;rsquo;s Your Target? Defining Your Homeownership Goal # This is where you move from daydreaming to doing.</description></item><item><title>How Much to Save Per Paycheck (how much to save per paycheck): A Practical Guide</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/how-much-to-save-per-paycheck/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 06:47:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/how-much-to-save-per-paycheck/</guid><description>If you’ve ever wondered how much to save from each paycheck, you’re not alone. The classic rule of thumb is to aim for 20% of your take-home pay. This isn&amp;rsquo;t just a random number; it&amp;rsquo;s the savings portion of the popular 50/30/20 budget, a simple framework that can really build a strong financial foundation.
Think of it as the starting line. Hitting that 20% mark helps you get into the rhythm of paying yourself first, which is crucial for tackling debt, building an emergency fund, and investing for the long haul.</description></item><item><title>A Simple Guide to Income and Expenses</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/income-and-expenses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:46:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/income-and-expenses/</guid><description>Getting a handle on your money really just comes down to one thing: the relationship between your income and expenses. It’s a simple idea. Income is what comes in, and expenses are what goes out. The whole game of financial wellness is just making sure more money is coming in than going out, consistently.
The Foundation of Financial Wellness # Picture your finances as an old-school balancing scale. On one side, you&amp;rsquo;ve got all the money flowing into your life—your income.</description></item><item><title>The 12 Best Monthly Expense Tracker Printable Resources for 2026</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/monthly-expense-tracker-printable/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 07:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/monthly-expense-tracker-printable/</guid><description>In a world of apps and automated tools, the simple act of writing down your expenses offers a powerful, tangible connection to your financial habits. A monthly expense tracker printable provides a clean slate each month to mindfully log spending, identify patterns, and gain direct control over your cash flow. This hands-on approach forces a moment of reflection with every entry, turning a passive task into an active financial decision. It’s a method that works for anyone, from families managing a complex household budget to individuals focused on privacy and debt payoff.</description></item><item><title>The Ultimate List of Household Expenses for 2026: 10 Categories to Track</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/list-of-household-expenses/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:56:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/list-of-household-expenses/</guid><description>Building a solid financial foundation starts with one simple, yet powerful, step: knowing exactly where your money goes. For many individuals, couples, and families, gaining a complete picture of spending feels overwhelming. Small, untracked purchases and overlooked recurring bills can easily lead to budget overruns, strained conversations about money, and missed savings goals. This is where a comprehensive list of household expenses becomes an indispensable tool, transforming financial chaos into clarity.</description></item><item><title>How to Reduce Monthly Expenses A Practical Guide for Real Life</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/how-to-reduce-monthly-expenses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/how-to-reduce-monthly-expenses/</guid><description>Before you can start cutting costs, you need to figure out where your money is actually going. It sounds obvious, but most of us have only a vague idea. This first step isn&amp;rsquo;t about making drastic changes; it&amp;rsquo;s about getting an honest, clear picture of your spending habits. Think of it as creating a map—you can&amp;rsquo;t plan a new route until you know your starting point.
Your Starting Point: Finding Where Your Money Really Goes # Feeling the squeeze from rising costs?</description></item><item><title>v0.8.1 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.8.1-release/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.8.1-release/</guid><description>The v0.8.1 release introduces enhanced Import functionality. This update gives users the flexibility to override any fields during the import process, offering greater control over data management.
GitHub releases # Econumo: v0.8.1</description></item><item><title>How to Stick to a Budget That Actually Works for You</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/how-to-stick-to-a-budget/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 06:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/how-to-stick-to-a-budget/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s get one thing straight: the secret to sticking with a budget isn&amp;rsquo;t about having superhuman willpower. It’s about making your plan realistic, easy to see, and something you can work on with others. Forget thinking of a budget as a financial straitjacket. Instead, see it as a flexible guide that helps you line up your everyday spending with what you truly want out of life.
Why Most Budgets Fail and How Yours Can Succeed # Anyone can start a budget.</description></item><item><title>v0.8.0 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.8.0-release/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.8.0-release/</guid><description>The v0.8.0 release introduces Import/Export functionality. This allows users to easily back up their data or migrate between different instances of Econumo.
Changelog # Breaking Changes: EconumoFamilyBundle code merged into EconumoBundle and removed. No functionality changes. Deprecated: The System API was deprecated in version 0.8.0 and will be removed in version 1.0.0. Introduced CSV Import/Export functionality. Introduced command ./bin/console app:update-currency-rates to update currency exchange rates from https://openexchangerates.org as a replacement for the separate tool.</description></item><item><title>A Practical Guide to Budgeting for Irregular Income</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/budgeting-for-irregular-income/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:53:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/budgeting-for-irregular-income/</guid><description>When your income swings up and down each month, standard budgeting advice can feel like it was written for a different planet. The key to getting a handle on things isn&amp;rsquo;t about guessing what you&amp;rsquo;ll earn next month. Instead, it&amp;rsquo;s about creating a rock-solid plan based on your absolute essentials.
This means building what I call a &amp;lsquo;bare-bones&amp;rsquo; budget. You figure out the bare minimum you need to get by and base your entire financial plan on that number.</description></item><item><title>How to Budget as a Couple: The Practical Guide</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/how-to-budget-as-a-couple/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:39:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/how-to-budget-as-a-couple/</guid><description>Before you even think about spreadsheets or budgeting apps, the first real step in managing money as a couple is simply talking. Seriously. The most successful shared budgets are built on open, honest conversations about your financial histories, habits, and dreams. This chat is the real bedrock of your financial life together.
Starting the Money Talk Without the Tension # Let&amp;rsquo;s be honest: the &amp;ldquo;money talk&amp;rdquo; can feel heavy. It’s rarely just about the numbers.</description></item><item><title>How to Create a Household Budget That Actually Works for Couples</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/how-to-create-a-household-budget/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 03:50:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/how-to-create-a-household-budget/</guid><description>Getting a handle on your household budget starts with a simple, honest chat. Before you get into the weeds of where your money should go, you and your partner need to sit down together, gather up all your income sources, and list out every single fixed expense. Think of it less as a math problem and more as the first step in teamwork. It’s all about creating a clear, shared picture of your financial starting point.</description></item><item><title>v0.7.0 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.7.0-release/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.7.0-release/</guid><description>The v0.7.0 release introduces PostgreSQL support in beta. Since it’s still in beta, it has performance issues, so it’s not recommended for use.
GitHub releases # Econumo: v0.7.0</description></item><item><title>v0.6.0 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.6.0-release/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.6.0-release/</guid><description>The v0.6.0 release features a complete rewrite of how Econumo handles numbers and currencies. This update allows the system to utilize the specified number of fraction digits for each currency (8 maximum), ensuring precise budget conversions, even for older periods.
After deploying this version, it is recommended to run the following command:
docker-compose exec -u www-data econumo bin/console app:restore-currency-fraction-digits Changelog # Enhanced the command docker-compose exec -u www-data econumo bin/console app:add-currency --help, enabling you to specify a custom name and the number of fraction digits for any currency, including Bitcoin.</description></item><item><title>v0.5.2 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.5.2-release/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.5.2-release/</guid><description>The v0.5.2 release primarily includes bug fixes and minor improvements based on feedback from the Reddit community following the announcement of Econumo CE.
Changelog # Fixed the bug related to multiple currencies without their exchange rates. GitHub releases # Econumo: v0.5.2</description></item><item><title>v0.5.1 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.5.1-release/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.5.1-release/</guid><description>The v0.5.1 release primarily includes bug fixes and minor improvements based on feedback from the Reddit community following the announcement of Econumo CE.
Changelog # Fixed the display of multiple expense transactions with the same category in the budget. Added a placeholder for the transaction entry form. Resolved issues with the date range functionality in the budget. Added a &amp;ldquo;Shared Access&amp;rdquo; page to Econumo CE. Fixed the /api/v1/system/import-currency-rates endpoint to update existing exchange rates without returning a 500 error.</description></item><item><title>v0.5.0 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.5.0-release/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.5.0-release/</guid><description>Changelog # Added user onboarding. Added more icons for categories. Added a calculator widget for the transaction dialog. Refactored logic related to budget loading. Refactored the BudgetAccessModal component. Refactored the BudgetChangeCurrency component. Improved handling of the long-press directive. Fixed issue where new envelopes were created in the second position instead of the first. Corrected currency conversion for the &amp;ldquo;Available&amp;rdquo; field in the budget module. Fixed bug that occurred when clearing cache after deleting a budget.</description></item><item><title>v0.4.3 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.4.3-release/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.4.3-release/</guid><description> Changelog # Added &amp;ldquo;Total&amp;rdquo; amount to the budgeting module. GitHub releases # Econumo: v0.4.3</description></item><item><title>v0.4.1 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.4.1-release/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.4.1-release/</guid><description> Changelog # Updated email content. Added the ECONUMO_BASE_URL environment variable. Fixed a bug related to the default locale. GitHub releases # Econumo: v0.4.1</description></item><item><title>v0.4.0 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.4.0-release/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.4.0-release/</guid><description>Changelog # Added a registration feature and updated the configuration and login layout. Corrected the translation for &amp;ldquo;All accounts.&amp;rdquo; Fixed budget calculations for individual users. Resolved issues with the modal window displaying the transaction list for budgets. Introduced user avatars in the transaction list modal for budgets. Fixed a bug that displayed ghost transactions when a user changed a transaction type. Improved the currency selection box in the Budget module.</description></item><item><title>v0.3.0 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.3.0-release/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.3.0-release/</guid><description> Changelog # Econumo Family and Econumo One merged into Econumo CE and were fully open-sourced. Econumo Cloud became Econumo. Fixed a problem with currency rates for the Budget module. GitHub releases # Econumo: v0.3.0</description></item><item><title>v0.2.3 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.2.3-release/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.2.3-release/</guid><description> Changelog # Disabled a portion of the login form for the custom backend API URL Updated links to the Privacy Policy and Terms of Service pages Added edition to the logo GitHub releases # Econumo: v0.2.3</description></item><item><title>v0.2.2 Econumo hotfix</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.2.2-release/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.2.2-release/</guid><description> Changelog # Rollback of the dependency update in composer.lock that broke authentication GitHub releases # Econumo: v0.2.2</description></item><item><title>v0.2.1 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.2.1-release/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.2.1-release/</guid><description> Changelog # Added functionality to connect registered users with one another automatically. GitHub releases # Econumo: v0.2.1</description></item><item><title>v0.2.0 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.2.0-release/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.2.0-release/</guid><description> Changelog # Removed the legacy PostgreSQL dependency. Added an X-Timezone header to each API request to maintain consistent time zones between the frontend and backend. Addressed all of Rector&amp;rsquo;s warnings. Removed the old analytics API. Update API documentation. GitHub releases # Econumo: v0.2.0</description></item><item><title>v0.1.0 Econumo release</title><link>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.1.0-release/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/posts/v0.1.0-release/</guid><description>The first public release of Econumo.
GitHub releases # Econumo: v0.1.0</description></item></channel></rss>