<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on Econumo</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on Econumo</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://econumo.com/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Econumo API</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/api/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/api/</guid><description>Econumo API # Econumo includes a REST API and OpenAPI (Swagger) documentation.
The Swagger UI is accessible at the api/doc URL. For example, in the demo environment, it can be found here: https://demo.econumo.com/api/doc.
The documentation features only GET and POST HTTP methods. The GET method is used for reading data, while the POST method is used for modifying data (creating, changing, or deleting).
In this section # Econumo API System endpoints Health check Econumo API # All methods except those under /api/v1/system are part of the User API.</description></item><item><title>Econumo apps</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/apps/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/apps/</guid><description>Econumo APPs # Econumo is a web application, but you can also use it as a regular mobile application on your iPhone, Android device, Mac, or PC.
On iPhone: # Open the website https://app.econumo.com in Safari. Tap the Share button (square with an upward arrow). Select Add to Home Screen from the menu. Rename the shortcut if desired, then tap Add. The web app will appear on your home screen and open in its own instance.</description></item><item><title>Econumo Editions</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/edition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/edition/</guid><description>Econumo Editions # Econumo provides versatile editions to meet various needs:
Econumo # Suited for individuals and families seeking convenience and access, this cloud-hosted solution offers a comprehensive suite of financial management tools available anytime, anywhere.
Demo: https://demo.econumo.com Demo version is available for one week only. After this period, your demo account will be blocked.
Econumo CE (Community Edition) # Designed for households needing a self-hosted, collaborative approach. This free platform delivers powerful financial management features for those who prioritize privacy and control over their budgeting.</description></item><item><title>Contact us</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/contact-us/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/contact-us/</guid><description>Contact us # Please use GitHub discussions to talk about the roadmap, features, and bugs.
For billing-related inquiries or partnership opportunities, email econumo@gmail.com.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://econumo.com/docs/faq/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://econumo.com/docs/faq/</guid><description>Frequently Asked Questions # Do you have plans to add automated import of transactions from banks? # Automated import of transactions from banks and other sources is not a priority at this point. However, it might be added in the future as an optional feature.
As an alternative, you can use CSV import.
If you have development skills and want to contribute, you are welcome to do so by using Econumo&amp;rsquo;s API.</description></item></channel></rss>